Hello everyone and welcome to another leggings video and I'm super happy about
this video because I've planned it for a while now and I'm finally able to
present to you my cooperation with Ishtar and Brut for made to measure
leggings and tights. A lot of you have been asking also on Instagram what I
think of Ishtar and Brut and I was always like I can't tell you I don't own
some of the products but now it's time and I do have this leather look-alike
leggings and also a super shiny grey tights and I'm going to try both. So
what's the difference between ICHTA and BERUT and other leggings companies? They do
make everything made to measure so there's no stock when they receive the
measurements they make the pattern and the garment itself for the order and I'm
I'm going to try these on because they are made to my measurements.
Oh, super happy!
I don't even know, I'm kind of at a loss for words because
they tick every box, they're long enough, they feel great, they're super comfortable,
they make no camel toe, but they make a great booty, and yeah, I'm speechless.
They're so cool.
I really like the look in the mirror
this is like the perfect fit and it's because of the made to measure option or it's not an option
they only offer made to measure garments so there is no additional made to measure price and
And one advice, get help for taking your measurements.
So you don't have to do it alone.
So for example, if I want to measure my waist to floor, how am I supposed to see now?
Or maybe I would bend over and then the measurement would be totally wrong.
So if you send your measurements to Ishtar and Brut, they cross-check them.
And if there is some irregularity, they'll get back to you.
But if you have someone to help you even better or ask Ishtar and Brut,
they offer help via Skype if you're really at loss. This is just a plain and simple combination.
I'm wearing my Pleasant Moon and as you can see the leggings are totally long enough and some
like mesh top but I'm going to switch into my go-to leggings combination top in a second.
So I went for the full faux leather look now.
The leather red leggings have a firm waistband and this is the normal model, so there's also
a sportive model.
And although I called them leather red because they look a bit like faux leather or wet look,
they're actually coated spandex with real lycra so they're super stretchy and super
comfortable and one thing I totally love is that when I'm pulling them up here
they stay in place in the front they don't make any camel toe and when I'm
pulling them in my butt they make a great butt shape. Totally love them.
Some quick facts about Ischter & Brood as a company. They've been founded over 10 years
ago they're from the Netherlands so hello to the neighbor country and they
actually started like with sewing machines from the attic as a one-person
show now they do have a big workshop with a lot of advanced technology and a
lot of equipment and have a look at the homepage they have a lot of materials
and you can choose from these kind of four-letter stuff PVC spandex they take
whatever have a look I'll link it down below these are definitely my new
favorite leggings because they're so comfortable and they fit so great and I
already knew that before I recorded the video because I tried them on on the
forehand but I didn't try the tights and they're also made to measure which I
think is something totally unusual for tights so let's have a look now you can
And already tell they're super smooth and feel super great.
Before I'm going to get fully dressed I wanted to shout out to you real quick because they
have also this booty cut here and a waistband which is not firm but really stretchy and
comfortable so they are kind of unique I don't know with this cut and the make to measure
option and also this fabric is so smooth but I'm going to get dressed. But before I'm going to get
dressed I'm going to show you the difference between this made to measure cut and normal
tight really short. I don't think I have to say very much you can already see that the booty is
not pressed flat in the Eastern Brood tights and it enhances the butt shape and it's way better than
your normal average tights. I chose a plain black little dress because the tights are the eye
catcher still together with the heels they look fabulous and they are so shiny. I love them and
they're super comfortable really. They're not annoying, they're not too tight, they are stretchy
so they're kind of perfect. This is a ultra thin fabric, a nylon knit fabric with a lycra and
you can really feel that it's kind of smooth smooth so compared to this smooth dress the
tights are even smoother and I don't know feel even better. I think you have to feel it for
yourself to know what I mean. Let me know if you have any Ishtar and Brut leggings and what you
think of them or let me know what your favorite style today was. How do you like this shiny tights?
I'm curious so leave a comment. Thanks for watching this video. Also thanks to Ishtar and Brut for
this cooperation. I'm super happy about it and yeah I think that was it for today.
see you in the next video bye